<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Digital Privacy Advocacy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Digital Privacy Advocacy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:06:07 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Show The Back Of Your National ID to Anyone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dont-show-your-national-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 06:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dont-show-your-national-id/</guid>
      <description>In light of research conducted by a cybersecurity firm in the Philippines, it has been discovered that both the physical and digital versions of the Philippine Identification System ID, or more commonly known as the National ID, have critical security flaws that can allow potential theft and fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Tools That Help Protect Your Web Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/eight-tools-web-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 06:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/eight-tools-web-privacy/</guid>
      <description>In an age where your online privacy is under constant threat from tracking, data breaches, and surveillance, taking control of your digital footprint is more important than ever. Here are eight tools that will help protect your web privacy:&#xA;1. uBlock Origin uBlock Origin&#xA;uBlock Origin is a web content blocker that removes ads, trackers, and other annoyances from your web browsing experience. Created in 2014 by Raymond Hill, uBlock Origin can reduce the risk of spyware, malware and tracking mechanisms embedded in webpages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 06:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-is-privacy/</guid>
      <description>According to Dictionary.com, privacy is:&#xA;the state of being free from unwanted or undue intrusion or disturbance in one&amp;rsquo;s private life or affairs; freedom to be let alone.&#xA;More simply, privacy means having control over who knows information about you and what information they know.&#xA;For example, when you go to the bathroom, you close the door because you want to have privacy. You don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone else to see you using the toilet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
